It's Reiner!
Eren!
Seems to me this fight's over.
We've used the last of our strength.
As for Reiner,
I can't exactly kill him at this point.
Okay, fine.
Then let's go back home.
See you later, Reiner.
Guard the ship from any hostiles below.
If you've still got ammo,
then now's the time to use it.
Looks like they're retreating.
Does this mean we're safe?
They're getting away.
Gabi!
Eren Jaeger!
You won't escape!
I'll shoot you down.
Well, aren't you a filthy sight?
It's like you fell in
a pile of shit, Eren.
Captain Levi.
This takes me back, Eren.
You have a real kickable face,
you know that?
Once you're tied up,
I'd like to have a longer chat.
That's all right by me,
but I explained everything
in the letters I wrote.
Did you not understand them?
Tch. I know that face.
I used to see it on the rotten shits
I met in the underground.
Never thought I'd see it on you.
Hey, cheer up.
Everything went just like you wanted.
Stop 'em!
Kill every last devil you can!
Everyone get inside!
If they had guns that
could take down an airship,
they'd've brought them out by now.
Jean! You go in, too.
I'll keep an eye on things.
Understood, Commander Lobov!
We're counting on you, sir!
I already told you.
I'm just a recruit now!
Our people don't need
the Garrison anymore!
And that goes double for
the overpaid geezers in charge of it!
Jean!
Grab on!
Thanks, you two.
Who's left?
We're still waiting on Lima Squad.
But assuming that
all of them make it back,
we've lost six soldiers.
Right. Shit.
That's nothing compared to
the damage we did to the enemy.
Good work, soldiers!
We just fought the New
Eldian Empire's first battle
and it ended in victory!
Yeah!
That's right! Celebrate!
That's how we'll pay tribute
to our six fallen heroes!
Our first battle.
I wonder how many more
we'll have to fight.
How many more'll have to die?
Honestly, I'm just glad that we made it.
I know this isn't fair to the others,
but you guys will always
be special... to me.
That hurts, dumbass.
Don't hug us while you've
got all that metal on.
What'd you call me?
You're the only dumbass I see here.
Always playing with that
sorry excuse for a beard.
Huh?
Yeah, Conny's right!
Even if you could grow a real beard,
it's not like you could eat it.
Huh?!
Speaking of, are we eating soon?
No. Not till
we reach the island.
Seriously? Some leader you are.
Gabi!
Come on, Gabi, hold on a second!
Stop. It's over.
They're flying away, Gabi.
There's no point in chasing them.
Even you know that.
They killed our friends.
Zofia was right next to me, talking,
and then she was crushed
by a flying rock.
Udo tried to get it off her, but
that just got him trampled by the crowd.
They stepped on his head again and again
till it cracked open.
I ran into those gate guards we talk to,
and they yelled at me
'cause I was trying to
go back to the plaza.
They said it was too dangerous.
They tried to protect me
even though I'm Eldian.
Now they're dead.
I saw some woman
shoot them from a rooftop.
Because I'm an Eldian who was
born in this internment zone,
people spit at the sight
of me walking around.
I have lots of memories
of getting treated like dirt,
but they're the reason I try so hard.
I'm fighting to show the world
that the Eldians here are good people!
I made it this far because
I believed that someday
we could be proud of these armbands.
I did everything I could
to make that happen,
but now it's all been crushed.
This internment zone is my home!
I know it isn't perfect, but its
where the people I love live.
So if somebody tramples it,
I'm not gonna forgive them.
So why?
Why would you tell me not to chase them?
Mister Zeke was killed
right in front of us.
Don't you wanna do something?
Don't you wanna know why
all these people had to die?
So why, Reiner?
Tell me why my mom was eaten by a Titan.
Their home was trampled, too.
Huh?
That's why.
Our warriors attacked them years ago
and killed lots of people.
This is just revenge.
So did you see that happen?
Well no. I didn't.
Neither did I, Falco.
It doesn't matter.
These island devils threaten
world peace, remember?
We were taught all about them.
They're savage and cruel
and whatever we might've done to them,
it wasn't half as bad
as what they deserved.
Those devils aren't like us.
Reiner. I'm the same as you.
Same where I'm from.
Inside the walls, we're all just people.
Lima Squad's in.
That makes everyone.
All troops accounted for!
Tell the bridge we're good to ascend!
Got it!
It's just a kid!
I shot him down.
The line. It's still attached.
Gabi!
What do you think you're trying to do?
It's this trigger.
If I pull it, then...
Hold on. You wanna go up?
Don't be crazy.
I'll kill as many island devils as I can.
Stop being an idiot,
you're just gonna get yourself killed!
Talk to my mom and dad for me.
Talk to Reiner and the others, too.
Tell them that I fought
my hardest, to the end.
Even if I'm killed up there,
all of you will carry
my spirit forward, right?
Falco! Gabi!
Are you two okay?
What're you doing out here?
It's Colt.
This is it, Falco.
You take care.
You're one of the good ones.
Surpass Gabi to protect her.
Spare her from the dark future we face.
Falco!
Falco?
Why come with me?
Because I'm the one who should
inherit the Armored Titan.
You hear me?
Huh?
Hey, Jean, did you hear a sound just now?
Hey! Quiet down for a second.
Make some noise! To victory!
Yeah!
Guys.
Hey. Lobov isn't back yet.
Weird. He should've
come back a while ago.
Sasha!
Take that, you Marleyan bastards!
Sasha! Sasha!
Hey. Stay with me.
Hey!
Why are you so loud...?
Are we eating soon or what?
She's bleeding! Find us
some bandages! Hurry!
Right!
Come on. Just hang in there.
Meat...
Jean. Lobov's dead.
They shot him and climbed
aboard using his ODM gear.
I'll toss 'em
outside. All right?
Do you really think
tossing kids out of an airship
is gonna help us stop all this killing?
What happened to Braun and Grice?
They ran off.
Neither one of them said
where they were going.
I haven't seen 'em since.
Hey, Pieck.
Commander. I remember now.
I know that Marleyan soldier.
The one who led us away from
the plaza and into a trap.
I know exactly where I saw them last.
It was about three years ago
during an inspection
of the first survey fleet
to go to Paradis,
after Reiner came back from his mission.
Wait, the scout ships that disappeared?
Yeah. I'm sure of it.
That beard looked so unnatural on them.
Hey. How long are you gonna
make me look at that thing?
What's your problem?
Everyone else likes it.
Are they still celebrating our "victory"?
Let go of me!
You haven't defeated us yet,
you filthy island devils!
You might've killed Zeke,
but not his spirit!
We'll carry his will forward!
Gabi. Stop!
What do we do with 'em, Jean?
Us true Eldians are gonna haunt you
till you're all rotting in the ground.
You tell that to the bastard
who planned this once I'm dead!
Think I'll just take you to him.
Then you can tell him yourself.
Sound good to you?
How were you able to recognize them?
Well. The soldier
happened to be
someone I had a personal interest in.
Because she's a devout
follower of Zeke Jaeger.
Gabi, Falco?
How did you get here?
What about you?
We thought that you were dead.
They took you alive?
But how is that possible?
Why would you let them?
Who the hell are these kids?
They somehow killed Lobov,
and then used his gear to climb aboard.
This one shot Sasha
before we could catch her.
I don't think she's gonna make it.
I'll leave the rest to you, Onyankopon.
I'm on it, Hange!
Well, Zeke.
It seems everything's
played out just like you wanted.
Wouldn't you say?
I did make a few miscalculations,
but aside from that, I would.
Zeke?
Huh? Wait, who are these kids?
Miscalculations.
Damn it, Yelena!
Why didn't you lock down
the Cart Titan and Jaw Titan
like you said you would?
We lost good people because of you!
I'm sorry.
I can assure you that
they both fell into the pit,
but it's still my fault.
Guess that's why you threw
more rocks at us than planned.
You had to put on a show
for your comrades, didn't ya?
Quite the performance,
coming from a mangy furball.
Yeah. Well done.
Aw. Please don't glare, Levi.
You don't wanna make me
piss my pants, do you?
And you gave quite
the performance, yourself.
Considering how bad you wish
you could actually kill me.
I'm the kind of person
who saves the best bite
for the end of my meal.
I can really savor the taste that way.
We killed Marley's brass
and took out their
primary fleet and port.
That oughtta buy us some time.
Before the whole world
comes crashing down on us
with a coordinated attack, you mean.
Every single time you
get yourself caught,
we give up lives to get you back.
No matter how high the cost, we pay it.
You noticed that trend
and used it against us.
Held yourself hostage to force our hand.
We had no choice except
to do what you wanted.
You put your trust in us,
and we've lost our trust in you, Eren.
You gain from this, too.
You now possess the Founding Titan
as well as a Titan with royal blood.
All your comrade's sacrifices
are about to bear fruit at last.
Eldia will be free.
It's Sasha.
She just died.
Conny.
Did Sasha... leave you...
any last words?
She asked... for some meat.
Can you guys keep a secret,
'cause I totally just helped
myself to the Officer's Pantry.
But hey. It'll be all right.
I mean once we've taken our land back,
we'll have all the room
we need for livestock!
Eren.
Sasha only died because you
dragged the Scouts into this.
You know that?
Was there some other
hidden path they could've taken?
The immutable past renders
that question irrelevant.
They have no choice
but to continue down
the path before them.
Next episode:
"Brave Volunteers."